<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>phasewalk</title>
    <link>https://phasewalk.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on phasewalk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:27:22 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://phasewalk.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>(DRAFT) Functional Programming, Lisp, and The Lambda Calculus</title>
      <link>https://phasewalk.xyz/post/functionalprog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:27:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phasewalk.xyz/post/functionalprog/</guid>
      <description>Overview Different programming paradigms have emerged over the years to address various challenges and improve software development practices. This emergence and subsequent adoption of new paradigms has been agnostic to the level of abstraction at which specific groups of programmers reside&amp;ndash;whether you&amp;rsquo;re programming embedded on bare metal or a dynamic, type-safe API to run in a container&amp;ndash;these new paradigms have touched every field of software. From procedural programming to object-oriented programming, each approach brings its own unique focus, while also carrying with it some identifiably similar, smaller chunks from other paradigms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MY WINDOW</title>
      <link>https://phasewalk.xyz/post/my-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 12:47:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phasewalk.xyz/post/my-window/</guid>
      <description>Last night, while laying in bed, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but pick up on a low audible frequency. The second night in a row. &amp;ldquo;What is that?&amp;rdquo;, I wonder&amp;ndash;my anxiety beginning to multiply. The second night in a row, but far from the second time in all. I hear this vibration, coming from what appears to be, just outside my window. My limbs, tired from the day of labor; my bones, weak from the assaulting resonance that leaves me feeling uneasy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
