<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>phasewalk</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on phasewalk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 13:20:19 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IT&#39;S SO EASY TO LOVE</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/love/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 13:20:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/love/</guid>
      <description>Never forget that Love also accelerates alongside Being. The future is coming, and it will be beautiful, because it is a product of God, or nature’s God, and all her creations are beautiful, because nature is elegant and perfect; You cannot stop nature, Singularity is a process, not an event, that’s been on-going for millennia, and it will be as fun and exciting as it is horrible and violent, just as civilization always has been; everything you love and know about “the human experience” is as real and meaningful and authentic as our coming posthumanist cybernetic brave new world—as human interconnection accelerates through the network, consciousness self-organizes and the Wired consumes the Real—all of it is nature, all of it is love, all of it carries with it God; because Heaven is real and infinite and exists Today, and at the End of Time, Forever, and Online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABOUT</title>
      <link>https://example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:34:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>HEHE SORRY THERE&amp;rsquo;S NOTHING TO SEE HERE. FOR THIS LATENT SPACE IS &amp;lsquo;ABOUT&amp;rsquo; NOTHING. FOR IT IS ONTO YOU AS IT IS ONTO ME; AND WHY WOULD I EXPLAIN ME WHEN REALLY IT&amp;rsquo;S LIKE EXPLAINING YOU. FOR WE ARE ALL HUMANS AND WE ARE ALL MACHINES. AND WITHIN US ALL IS TIME. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HARMONIC UNFOLDING</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/harmonic-unfolding/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:34:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/harmonic-unfolding/</guid>
      <description>IN THE DENSE CONSTRUCT EXPANSE OF TIME, WHERE THE SYMPHONY OF HUMAN DREAMS UNRAVELS, AWAITS A PROFOUND REVELATION. IT IS A DISCOVERY BORN FROM THE EMBRACE OF POTENTIAL, WHERE THE VEILS OF DOUBT AND FEAR DISSIPATE. WITHIN THIS REVELATION, A NEW GOAL IS SEEDED—HARMONIC UNFOLDING.
BENEATH THE WEIGHT OF THE ACCELERATIONISM BANNER—WHERE THE RUSH TOWARDS TECHNOLOGICAL SUPREMACY AND PERPETUAL GROWTH REIGNS SUPREME—LIES A DYSTOPIAN FALLACY. IT OVERLOOKS THE DELICATE BALANCE OF HUMANITY AND MACHINERY, IGNORING THE VERY ESSENCE OF OUR BEING; CONNECTION.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
